Welcome to the new feature introduction video of Marvelous Designer 2025.
In this video, we will introduce you to the new version of the
Marvelous Designer 2025 model.
Let's start by taking a look at the overall display.
There are two different components.
The first component is that cool screen and the color is nice and golden.
The second component is that cool screen and the color is nice and golden.
In the window, the assets are classified into the following categories, such as clothing, virtual models, objects, accessories, and scenes.
Click on the preview bar in the upper right corner to open the preview interface and view the preview of the file.
There is an asset bar under each category. Here you can find your default assets.
In addition, there is also a Connect asset category, which is the assets sold in the official mall.
When you click on the free option, the assets displayed are free assets.
If you cancel the free option, you can browse and purchase more paid products.
You can check the purchase page of the shop on the website to see the products you have purchased.
You can also visit the Closet platform in the new library window.
Closet is a cloud platform that can be used to upload, share, and manage your 3D assets.
We can download the project files that were previously uploaded from Closet, then go to the shop page to check and add the assets needed.
Here I searched for an oversize top and added it to the 3D window.
And here it is.
Once you've read the manual and found the right task, you can use the 3D window to read the layout.
You can also change the size of your 3D wall and make the wall a little smaller.
You can change the location of the new clothes by adding layers to the new clothes.
This allows the clothes to move quickly and circle out.
Next, we will remove the button that holds the outer clothes and adjust the layout of the shirt.
After wearing it, we can browse the fabric in the store and select the fabric we like and apply it to the clothing.
You can also browse other digital assets according to the need to call them.
You can also build your own asset library to manage assets more effectively.
You can click on the Create new asset library button at the top of the menu.
Then, click on Add asset, and then select the asset in the computer.
Now, we will save the asset to the asset we just added.
Then, click on the refresh button to view the content saved in the asset.
You can manage your assets through these documents.